
var questions = 
      [
        {
          question:"[1]. How many letters does 'English alphabet' have?",
          option1:"A. 26",
          option2:"B. 24",
          option3:"C. 0",
          option4:"D. 15",
          answer: 4
        },
        
        {
          question: "[2]. How many holes in POLO?",
          option1:"A.1",
          option2:"B.I don't Know",
          option3:"C.3",
          option4:"D.May be 2?",
          answer: 3
        },
        {
          question: "[3]. 7-1=?",
          option1:"A. 6",
          option2:"B. MATHS",
          option3:"C. GermanyVsBrazil",
          option4:"D. Subtraction",
          answer: 4
        },
        {
          question: "[4]. Which one is odd here? DUMB,STUPID,YOU,ONE",
          option1:"A. ONE",
          option2:"B. STUPID",
          option3:"C. DUMB",
          option4:"D. ME ofcourse!",
          answer: 1
        },
        {
          question: "[5]. What is this?",
          option1:"A. A stupid Game",
          option2:"B. A word",
          option3:"C. A question",
          option4:"D. This is fun!",
          answer: 4
        },
        {
          question: "[ ]. <- What should be the question number here?",
          option1:"A. Can't remember",
          option2:"B. 7",
          option3:"C. 6",
          option4:"D. prev question no. + 1",
          answer: 3
        },
        {
          question: "[7]. What is missing from this question.",
          option1:"1. Logic",
          option2:"2. Question mark",
          option3:"3. A point",
          option4:"4. An answer",
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "[8]. 22/10=?",
          option1:"1. 4",
          option2:"2. 2",
          option3:"3. 20.2",
          option4:"4. 22.2",
          answer: 2
        },
        {
          question: "[9]. NAC UOY REWSNA SIHT?",
          option1:"A. Wut?",
          option2:"B. Did not understand",
          option3:"C. ON",
          option4:"D. !SEY",
          answer: 4
        },
        {
          question: "[10]. Can you get this question wrong?",
          option1:"A. NOPE!",
          option2:"B. No way!!",
          option3:"C. Yeah",
          option4:"D. NO! I want the big 'SURPRISE'!",
          answer: 4
        },
        
      ];
